Everyone is acknowledging that you are
the first founder and looking at you.
Who are you? Is this Psycho Helmet-san?
How do you like all that clapping and
cheering you've never experienced before?
Well? Doesn't it feel great?
No, not at all.
Let's talk face to face.
I'm at the base of the broccoli.
Damn it, it's not a broccoli anymore.
Because this thing absorbed all
those emotions from those people,
it turned into something
completely different.
Have you ever strongly
believed in something?
The aggregation of powerful belief
can sometimes manifest into reality.
A great change is about
to happen in this world.
A new god named Psycho Helmet
is going to take physical form and ascend.
God?
You're just a coordinator for this group.
I'm going to claim that Psycho Helmet
is the reincarnation of their great creator.
I will lead the people down the right
path and give their hearts peace.
The right path?
Is giving people peace of mind even effective?
Who the hell knows?
I'm just making shit up.
Just pray five minutes a day
towards the Divine Tree.
That becomes my sustenance.
The followers will figure out the rest for me
with however they interpret this.
You look like you have
something you want to say.
But look, the believers are
all having a great time, too.
Including Ritsu and Reigen...
Whoops. He was an exception, though.
He figured me out before anyone else
and tried to shut all this down first.
In the end, the ones
who have the most fun win.
So you're the one who had
Master Reigen say that...
...Dimple.
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
I realized that my youth was grey
The root of this irritation is unknown
My brain runs parallel with this emotional train
Struggling adolescence
Don't disturb the subconscious mind
Who's that behind me?
Opposing ideas, distortion
Purge the sorrow
So, do what you can now.
My life
Finally
Break it down!!
(WANT) desire (YOUNG) and sincerity
(BURN) they begin to sprout (1) within my chest
(TRANCE) I won't awaken (CHANCE) but I want to
(STANCE) both sides of the coin
(1) are back-to-back
Accept me as I am
Conflicting freedom and relations
If they can become one
That smile will be
One and only "1"
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Mob Psycho 100 III"
"Mob Psycho 100 "
MOB MOB WOW! MOB MOB WOW!
One and only "1"
"Divine Tree 2
- Peace~"
Now, don't be so mad.
Hanazawa's fine.
More importantly,
join the Psycho Helmet Religion.
You and I can stand at the top
and have a blast together.
Why?
By the looks of it,
you're already powerful enough.
You still have potential to grow.
Looking at the future, I figured it'd be
a waste not to take advantage of that power.
I refuse.
Well, I figured that'd be
your answer for now.
But your family, your friends,
and everyone else
already live in a world where
they experience happiness
through their faith in Psycho Helmet-sama.
You're the only one left behind
in this city, Shigeo.
No one's ever coming back.
How long are you gonna be stubborn?
They're all just being brainwashed by you.
You're the one who needs to give up.
You mad?
I am.
Of course I'm mad.
Return everyone to their senses now.
You even got to Ritsu and Master Reigen...
How did you manage that?
The first stage was to have them
touch the Divine Tree
or have them ingest a bit of it somehow.
I got into their minds
through physical contact.
The second stage was to expose the few
left behind to the passion of the masses.
That's how I got to Reigen, too.
He was overwhelmed by his surroundings.
And now, we've entered the third stage.
That strong feeling of faith
transmits from one person to another.
It's only a matter of time till everyone
in the country believes in Psycho Helmet.
Then it'll really be something.
Then I'll truly become a new god.
I don't really get all this, but becoming
a god is even more pointless.
Do you really not understand
what you're doing?
Huh?
The whole city's a mess.
The city?
"Unnatural Deterioration of Home"
"Unnatural Deterioration of Home" I didn't know
that, but we can just rebuild it all later.
I didn't know that, but we can
just rebuild it all later.
That's enough.
Just undo their brainwashing.
This isn't like you. You're being
very sentimental and narrow-minded.
You keep calling it brainwashing,
but it's actually not that bad.
It's not like I changed
any of their personalities,
much less their hobbies
or the things they like.
The way that Ritsu, Reigen,
and everyone in the Body Improvement Club
feel about you isn't going to change, either.
You're all just going to become followers
of the Psycho Helmet Religion.
And... you'll feel happiness in that and be able
to share that happiness with other believers.
I'm not trying to exclude you
from the fun here.
So... what, exactly, is your problem?
What am I doing wrong?
What are you doing wrong?
Dimple, you're playing dirty.
You're controlling people's hearts
with your power.
That means they can't defy you and you
can make them do whatever you want.
We live in a world where there are laws and
societal norms that we can't defy to begin with.
If you're oblivious to them,
you don't have any problems.
Not to mention, should I not listen to you,
won't you just resort to force
at the end of the day?
Sure, but I don't have a choice...
Because my family and friends
are being brainwashed.
Believe it or not, I'm restraining
myself quite a bit right now.
Wait, Kageyama-kun.
What Dimple-kun's doing isn't exactly evil.
What?
Think about this rationally.
If you choose violence just because
you don't agree with him, it's over.
No, there's still time.
The Psycho Helmet Religion
still hasn't officially begun.
No. If you put your hands on him,
it's all over.
Your relationship with Dimple-kun...
Our friendship will all be over.
If you're going to forcibly tear
apart the Psycho Helmet Religion,
I'm going to stop you.
Even if you defeat me,
your little brother and Reigen-san aren't
going to let you get away with this.
Eventually, everyone will stand in your way.
Dimple, you...
Hanazawa doesn't have
any bad intentions, either.
He's just trying to get you to change
your mind because he truly cares about you.
I told you, even if you don't do anything,
everyone's daily lives--
Dimple, come out.
I want to talk to you face to face.
Stop this, Kageyama-kun!
We've been talking this whole time.
If you're going to harm the Psycho
Helmet Religion or the Divine Tree,
then you'll have to deal with me!
Hanazawa-kun! Snap out of it!
Unfortunately for you,
I'm not controlling him.
I've just gained another
important thing in my life.
I'm going to keep fighting you until
you give up and leave, Kageyama-kun!
I'm sorry.
Dimple, show yourself!
Those who believe
are blessed with divinity.
Hanazawa has godly powers right now.
I'm overflowing with power...
Hana... zawa-kun...
I'm sorry.
Oh, no. I ended up hurting
the Divine Tree again.
Well done, Hanazawa.
Shigeo, if you let the Divine Tree's
roots embrace you and cool down,
you'll change your mind, too.
Such incredible power...
The broccoli's roots?
These roots are dangerous...
Get away from here, Hanazawa-kun!
Seriously, Kageyama-kun?!
Psycho Helmet-sama, get behind me!
W-Wow... You really are amazing!
Aw, damn it. Now you opened
a hole in the Divine Tree.
I mean, it'll close right back up anyway...
I guess becoming a god
isn't so easy after all, Shigeo.
It's futile.
Dimple, why?
Why won't you show yourself?
Could it be...
...you're scared of me?
Are we going to continue?
Enough. That's enough.
Don't make me feel like this.
Don't you get it, Dimple?
Come out, please.
Or else...
My powers... are being sucked away.
Correct.
You probably should've noticed
that a wee bit earlier.
It was a mistake to let yourself
be lured into the Divine Tree.
But your biggest mistake...
...was defying me.
Dimple... What's the meaning of this?!
Cool your head a bit.
If you're not gonna listen to me,
I might just get her to tell you.
Huh?
If I have Tsubomi-chan convince you,
maybe you'll finally cool off a bit.
Mob-kun! You can't go causing trouble for
everyone in the Psycho Helmet Religion!
Get a clue already!
You know?
Hey, now...
You get so serious anytime
Tsubomi-chan is involved.
While we're at it, I guess I'll
just finally break it to ya.
Shigeo, you've got no chance with her.
Huh?
Takane Tsubomi is the type of person to
honestly say she doesn't want something.
I tried to forcefully give her one of the
candies, but she batted his hand away.
Even when I used her friends
to get through to her,
she wasn't interested.
She's a strong woman who
doesn't conform to others
"Yakisoba" "Grilled Corn" She's a strong
woman who doesn't conform to others
"Yakisoba" "Grilled Corn"
and lives by her own set of values.
No wonder she never even noticed you
when you used your psychic
powers in front of her.
Even if you get shredded,
I'm sure she'll never need you.
But now... she's also part of
the Psycho Helmet Religion.
Meaning you might just be able to win
her over as the great founder Shigeo.
This is stupid.
Wow...
I thought we already took
most of your power...
But I guess you've still got some left.
Maybe I shouldn't have
shown myself just yet.
Well, whatever. It's not like
I'd lose to you right no--
W-Wait...
N-Now, wait a minute...
Don't get ahead of yourself, damn it!
This is how you repay my kindness?!
I guess I'm just gonna have
to get serious, too.
Watch closely.
This... is the newly, happily reborn...
"God Dimple"
...Great God Dimple!
So what?
Here I go!
Godly Punch!
Godly Dash!
And then...
...Godly Smash!
Well? How do you like the power of God?
You give up yet?
Godly Throw!
Godly...
...Sandbag!
Godly Straight!
I'm very aware, Shigeo...
...that this isn't enough to beat you.
But you should be at your limit soon...
The tremendous power that we sucked from him
is flowing into me through the Divine Tree.
I saw the limit of his power
when he fought Claw's boss.
His power isn't endless. It's finite.
He did almost lose to Mogami
Keiji's mental attacks, too.
He's not invincible!
I know how to defeat Kageyama
Shigeo more than any--
That's your true form?
That's your true identity?
You can't be serious.
Hmph. Don't worry.
I'll shut you up in a second!
I'll make you regret not
coming over to this side!
Is that what you really think?
Then you shouldn't be holding back.
Your powers, your actions, your words...
They're all fake.
Don't try to convince me
that's the real Dimple.
It's just...
It doesn't suit you. I won't allow it.
I won't accept it.
Who the hell do you think you are?!
You won't accept it?!
Don't go casually denying the thing
I've been wanting so badly!
Godly Beam!
Sh-Shit! I used too much energy!
Shigeo--
I-I can feel his rage.
W-Wait, wait...
That bastard still...
He still has this much power left?
I need to finish him off
before he gets to me.
That one was actually surprising.
I might've almost died.
A little more and I really
might lose all faith in you.
This is terrifying...
He's glaring at me with those eyes.
I just want to know how you
really feel. Say something, Dimple.
Don't give me that.
I was trying to take advantage
of you from the start!
I'm sad. So...
...is this goodbye, Dimple?
Is he coming at me?!
Behold my full psychic strength!
I'm going to end this!
Holy shit, that shirt is lame!
There was a blue light shining
I'm wide awake this 1:30 AM
What remained even after I swiped
Are the smiles of my friends right beside me
Yes, I want someone to understand...
This wish that's hidden colorless and invisible
The breath I was holding deep within my heart
I let it all out at once and return to my senses
On days that I'm feeling apathetic
it suddenly comes to mind
These seasons I spent as if they were a given
Even if reality becomes sullied
Only the sky we saw together is real
This is more incomprehensible
Than the grammar on the blackboard
If it's going to disappear within 24 hours
This flowing story is just too lonely
I just can't do it
Just like that back hip circle I gave up on
But I'm not going to...
Give up
My present anymore
I adorn my overflowing emotions
And run through my worries and hesitations
It can't be decided from 0 to 100
Draw the incomplete future with this hand
We can't even prove its existence
But as the world stabs the middle of my chest
It overflows with cobalt blue
English Translator: Michelle Tymon Translation Editor:
Zachary Carlysle Translation Checker: Sriram Gurunathan
Man, I never could relate to you, Shigeo.
I should've been able to use our psychic
powers and had a better life.
You really did know how to piss me off.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 6:
"Divine Tree 3
- Dimple Is~"
"Divine Tree 3 - Dimple Is~"
"Divine Tree 3 - Dimple Is~."
"Divine Tree 3
- Dimple Is~"